<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>wiki</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:34:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How Many Times Could Microsoft Buy Sony?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/microsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/microsoft/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;how-many-times-could-microsoft-buy-sony-a-look-at-their-market-capitalizations&#34;&gt;How Many Times Could Microsoft Buy Sony? A Look at Their Market Capitalizations&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The tech industry is known for its ever-changing landscape, with acquisitions often making headlines. But just how far does the financial power of giants like Microsoft stretch? A compelling thought experiment arises when comparing the market capitalizations of two major players: &lt;strong&gt;Microsoft&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Sony&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;microsofts-massive-market-cap&#34;&gt;Microsoft’s Massive Market Cap&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As of February 2025, &lt;strong&gt;Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s market capitalization&lt;/strong&gt; stands at approximately &lt;strong&gt;$3.045 trillion USD&lt;/strong&gt;. This immense figure reflects Microsoft’s dominant role in the tech space, from software to cloud computing, gaming, and artificial intelligence. With its diverse portfolio and global presence, Microsoft has solidified itself as a behemoth in the business world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>January25 news</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/january25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 18:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/january25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;tech-news---january-2025&#34;&gt;Tech News - January 2025&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;artificial-intelligence-and-cybersecurity&#34;&gt;Artificial Intelligence and Cybersecurity&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DeepSeek&amp;rsquo;s AI Model Release&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;On January 20, 2025, Chinese AI startup DeepSeek released the DeepSeek-R1 model, a large language model utilizing chain-of-thought reasoning. This model is open-source and claims performance comparable to OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s o1 across various tasks.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2025_in_artificial_intelligence?utm_source=chatgpt.com&#34;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s Stargate Project&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;On January 21, 2025, U.S. President Donald Trump announced the Stargate Project, a joint venture involving OpenAI, Oracle, SoftBank, and MGX. The project aims to build AI infrastructure in the U.S., with an estimated cost of $500 billion over four years.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2025_in_artificial_intelligence?utm_source=chatgpt.com&#34;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about&#34;&gt;About&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to &lt;strong&gt;Wiki &amp;amp; Blog&lt;/strong&gt;—a place where knowledge meets discussion! This site is designed to serve as both an &lt;strong&gt;informational wiki&lt;/strong&gt; and a &lt;strong&gt;dynamic blog&lt;/strong&gt;, covering a wide range of topics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-you&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You&amp;rsquo;ll Find Here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wiki Articles&lt;/strong&gt; – Well-structured, factual, and in-depth information on various topics.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blog Posts&lt;/strong&gt; – Opinion pieces, reviews, and insights from different perspectives.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guides &amp;amp; Tutorials&lt;/strong&gt; – Step-by-step instructions on various subjects.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Contributions&lt;/strong&gt; – Readers can contribute, discuss, and expand knowledge collaboratively.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-this-site&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why This Site?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I believe in open knowledge sharing. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking for &lt;strong&gt;technical guides, AI research, gaming insights, or general knowledge&lt;/strong&gt;, this platform provides well-organized content that evolves over time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Blocks DistroWatch Links: A Review of the Incident</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/facebook-blocks-distrowatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/facebook-blocks-distrowatch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;facebook-blocks-distrowatch-links-a-review-of-the-incident&#34;&gt;Facebook Blocks DistroWatch Links: A Review of the Incident&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In January 2025, Facebook blocked links to DistroWatch, a popular website dedicated to Linux distributions, resulting in warnings and account restrictions for users sharing these links. This incident sparked confusion and raised questions about the reliability and fairness of automated content moderation systems. This report reviews what happened, the reasons behind it, Facebook&amp;rsquo;s response, and the broader implications of overblocking.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Edge&#39;s New Scareware Blocker</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/microsoft-edge-scareware/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/microsoft-edge-scareware/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;stand-up-to-scareware-with-microsoft-edges-new-scareware-blocker&#34;&gt;Stand Up to Scareware with Microsoft Edge&amp;rsquo;s New Scareware Blocker&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Edge is taking a proactive step in protecting users from online scams with its new &lt;strong&gt;Scareware Blocker&lt;/strong&gt; feature. Now available in preview, this tool is designed to detect and block malicious full-screen pop-ups that attempt to deceive users into thinking their computer is infected.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-scareware&#34;&gt;What is Scareware?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Scareware refers to deceptive pop-ups that mimic legitimate security warnings, urging users to call a fake support number or download unnecessary (and often harmful) software. These scams use fear tactics, such as:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing Different AI Models</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/tic-tac-toe-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/tic-tac-toe-test/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;tic-tac-toe-ai-evaluation-report&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tic-Tac-Toe AI Evaluation Report&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This report evaluates several AI models for a Tic-Tac-Toe game, focusing on performance, design, and gameplay in different modes. The evaluation includes different versions of AI models: ChatGPT-4, Cloud 3.5-Sonnet, Copilot, Gemini 2.0 Flash, and Gemini 2.0 Flash-Experimental.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the promt was runed only once per AI&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-chatgpt-4&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. ChatGPT-4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speed&lt;/strong&gt;: Fast.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Player vs AI&lt;/strong&gt;: Works well, providing a smooth experience.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Design&lt;/strong&gt;: Simple, intuitive, but slightly lacking in aesthetics compared to others.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Issues&lt;/strong&gt;: Occasionally, the game incorrectly prints the letter &amp;ldquo;O&amp;rdquo; multiple times (twice or five times) without reason.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary&lt;/strong&gt;: ChatGPT-4 delivers a solid player vs. AI experience, but with minor glitches in output. The overall gameplay remains strong.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;2-cloud-35-sonnet&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Cloud 3.5-Sonnet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speed&lt;/strong&gt;: Slightly slower than ChatGPT-4.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Player vs AI&lt;/strong&gt;: Effective and functional. The AI behaves appropriately.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Design&lt;/strong&gt;: Good overall design with a clean interface and user-friendly features.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Issues&lt;/strong&gt;: None specific to functionality, but some users may prefer faster performance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary&lt;/strong&gt;: Cloud 3.5-Sonnet offers a reliable and visually appealing design with a slightly slower response time.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-copilot&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Copilot&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speed&lt;/strong&gt;: Slow.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Player vs AI&lt;/strong&gt;: Works, but the AI logic isn’t as responsive as the others.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Design&lt;/strong&gt;: The design is minimalistic, but the game lacks the player vs. player mode. Only player vs. AI is supported.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Issues&lt;/strong&gt;: Slow response times during AI turns can disrupt the gameplay experience.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary&lt;/strong&gt;: Copilot’s lack of player-vs-player mode and slower AI makes it less optimal for smooth gameplay, but the AI function is still decent.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;4-gemini-20-flash-experimental&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Gemini 2.0 Flash-Experimental&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speed&lt;/strong&gt;: Reasonably fast, but the AI responses can be slow.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Player vs AI&lt;/strong&gt;: The AI responds slower compared to other models, and during the AI turn, players can accidentally click and act as the AI.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Design&lt;/strong&gt;: Good design with a clean interface, although not as polished as the Cloud 3.5-Sonnet.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Issues&lt;/strong&gt;: The ability to click during AI turns can lead to confusing behavior.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary&lt;/strong&gt;: Gemini 2.0 Flash-Experimental has solid design and gameplay, but the AI responsiveness and interaction could be improved.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;5-gemini-20-flash&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Gemini 2.0 Flash&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speed&lt;/strong&gt;: Reasonable but inconsistent.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Player vs AI&lt;/strong&gt;: The player-vs-AI mode is non-functional, with only one mode available—AI vs AI.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Design&lt;/strong&gt;: The design is relatively weak, with unattractive buttons and interface elements.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Issues&lt;/strong&gt;: The mode switch functionality is absent, and the game doesn’t perform as expected with the player-vs-AI mode.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary&lt;/strong&gt;: Gemini 2.0 Flash has a weak design and lacks essential modes, making it less practical compared to the others.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;general-observations&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Observations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Design Consistency&lt;/strong&gt;: Models like Cloud 3.5-Sonnet and Gemini 2.0 Flash-Experimental offer the best visual experience, while Copilot and Gemini 2.0 Flash have room for improvement in design.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Functionality&lt;/strong&gt;: Most AI models work well for player vs AI, but only ChatGPT-4 and Cloud 3.5-Sonnet perform consistently in that mode. Copilot lacks player vs player support, and Gemini 2.0 Flash has severe limitations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speed&lt;/strong&gt;: While ChatGPT-4 and Gemini 2.0 Flash-Experimental provide faster gameplay, Copilot and Gemini 2.0 Flash fall behind in terms of response time.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For optimal performance and design in Tic-Tac-Toe gameplay, &lt;strong&gt;ChatGPT-4,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Gemini 2.0 Flash-Experimental,&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Cloud 3.5-Sonnet&lt;/strong&gt; are the best options. They offer smooth player vs. AI gameplay and decent design, though minor glitches in output may affect user experience. Copilot and Gemini 2.0 Flash fall short in certain areas, with Gemini 2.0 Flash not offering the expected player-vs-AI experience at all.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
