<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft on wiki</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/microsoft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Microsoft on wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:34:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/microsoft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How Many Times Could Microsoft Buy Sony?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/microsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/microsoft/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;how-many-times-could-microsoft-buy-sony-a-look-at-their-market-capitalizations&#34;&gt;How Many Times Could Microsoft Buy Sony? A Look at Their Market Capitalizations&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The tech industry is known for its ever-changing landscape, with acquisitions often making headlines. But just how far does the financial power of giants like Microsoft stretch? A compelling thought experiment arises when comparing the market capitalizations of two major players: &lt;strong&gt;Microsoft&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Sony&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;microsofts-massive-market-cap&#34;&gt;Microsoft’s Massive Market Cap&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As of February 2025, &lt;strong&gt;Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s market capitalization&lt;/strong&gt; stands at approximately &lt;strong&gt;$3.045 trillion USD&lt;/strong&gt;. This immense figure reflects Microsoft’s dominant role in the tech space, from software to cloud computing, gaming, and artificial intelligence. With its diverse portfolio and global presence, Microsoft has solidified itself as a behemoth in the business world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Edge&#39;s New Scareware Blocker</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/microsoft-edge-scareware/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/microsoft-edge-scareware/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;stand-up-to-scareware-with-microsoft-edges-new-scareware-blocker&#34;&gt;Stand Up to Scareware with Microsoft Edge&amp;rsquo;s New Scareware Blocker&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Edge is taking a proactive step in protecting users from online scams with its new &lt;strong&gt;Scareware Blocker&lt;/strong&gt; feature. Now available in preview, this tool is designed to detect and block malicious full-screen pop-ups that attempt to deceive users into thinking their computer is infected.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-scareware&#34;&gt;What is Scareware?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Scareware refers to deceptive pop-ups that mimic legitimate security warnings, urging users to call a fake support number or download unnecessary (and often harmful) software. These scams use fear tactics, such as:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
