<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cybersecurity on wiki</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/wiki-blogs/categories/cybersecurity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cybersecurity on wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/wiki-blogs/categories/cybersecurity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Apple’s Privacy U-Turn: Government Access to Your Data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wiki-blogs/post/this-is-sad-for-our-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wiki-blogs/post/this-is-sad-for-our-privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;apples-shift-on-privacy-a-compromise-with-government-surveillance&#34;&gt;Apple’s Shift on Privacy: A Compromise with Government Surveillance?&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-history-of-privacy-advocacy&#34;&gt;A History of Privacy Advocacy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Apple has long positioned itself as a champion of user privacy. The company famously clashed with the FBI in 2016 over unlocking an iPhone used by a terrorist, emphasizing that creating backdoors would weaken security for all users. Its strong encryption policies once set it apart from other tech giants.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;but-now-they-only-care-about-money&#34;&gt;But Now They Only Care About Money&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Apple&amp;rsquo;s policy shift is particularly evident in the UK, where the government has requested a backdoor into Apple’s encrypted services under the &lt;strong&gt;Investigatory Powers Act&lt;/strong&gt;, also known as the &lt;em&gt;Snooper&amp;rsquo;s Charter&lt;/em&gt;. This legislation requires tech companies to provide law enforcement with access to encrypted communications upon request.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Blocks DistroWatch Links: A Review of the Incident</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wiki-blogs/post/facebook-blocks-distrowatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wiki-blogs/post/facebook-blocks-distrowatch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;facebook-blocks-distrowatch-links-a-review-of-the-incident&#34;&gt;Facebook Blocks DistroWatch Links: A Review of the Incident&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &#xA;In January 2025, Facebook blocked links to DistroWatch, a popular website dedicated to Linux distributions, resulting in warnings and account restrictions for users sharing these links. This incident sparked confusion and raised questions about the reliability and fairness of automated content moderation systems. This report reviews what happened, the reasons behind it, Facebook&amp;rsquo;s response, and the broader implications of overblocking.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Edge&#39;s New Scareware Blocker</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wiki-blogs/post/microsoft-edge-scareware/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wiki-blogs/post/microsoft-edge-scareware/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;stand-up-to-scareware-with-microsoft-edges-new-scareware-blocker&#34;&gt;Stand Up to Scareware with Microsoft Edge&amp;rsquo;s New Scareware Blocker&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Edge is taking a proactive step in protecting users from online scams with its new &lt;strong&gt;Scareware Blocker&lt;/strong&gt; feature. Now available in preview, this tool is designed to detect and block malicious full-screen pop-ups that attempt to deceive users into thinking their computer is infected.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-scareware&#34;&gt;What is Scareware?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Scareware refers to deceptive pop-ups that mimic legitimate security warnings, urging users to call a fake support number or download unnecessary (and often harmful) software. These scams use fear tactics, such as:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
